// src/data/accordionData.js

const EmployeeWellnessData = {
    PrioritizeEmployeeWellbeing: [
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "Reduced Healthcare Costs",
            answer: "Promote preventive care to lower overall medical expenses.",
          },
          {
            id: "2",
            question: "Increased Productivity",
            answer: "Healthier, happier employees perform better and miss fewer workdays.",
          },
          {
            id: "3",
            question: "Stronger Corporate Culture",
            answer: "Demonstrate your commitment to employee wellbeing.",
          },
    ],
    ComprehensiveHealthcareServices: [
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "In-Clinic and Online Doctor Access",
            answer: "Connect with top doctors anytime, anywhere in India.",
          },
          {
            id: "2",
            question: "Pharmacy & Diagnostics",
            answer: "Claim up to 50% on prescriptions and tests bills .",
          },
          {
            id: "3",
            question: "Preventive Checkups",
            answer: "Complimentary annual health assessments.",
          },
    ],
    PersonalizedWellnessSolutions: [
        {
            id: "1",
            question: "Assessments",
            answer: "Comprehensive evaluations of physical and mental health.",
          },
          {
            id: "2",
            question: "Customized Plans",
            answer: "Tailored programs for fitness, nutrition, and stress management.",
          },
          {
            id: "3",
            question: "Ongoing Support",
            answer: "Annual Preventive Health Checkups and access to wellness professionals.",
          },
    ],
    OnSiteHealthServices: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Doctor Consultations ",
        answer: "Consult with any Allopathy, Homeopathy and Ayurvedic doctors.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Mental Health ",
        answer: "Counselling for stress, anxiety, and work-life balance.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Wellness Programs",
        answer: "Yoga, meditation, and healthy living workshops.",
      },
    ],
    TheOPDSureAdvantage: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Preventive Health Education",
        answer: "Major and Critical disease prevention and healthy living.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Vaccination Coverage",
        answer: "Protect your employees from infectious diseases or animal bits.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Health Education",
        answer: "Regular workshops on disease prevention and healthy living.",
      },
    ],
    ProvenBenefits: [
      {
        id: "1",
        question: "Reduced Costs",
        answer: "Preventive care lowers overall medical and insurance expenses.",
      },
      {
        id: "2",
        question: "Increased Engagement",
        answer: "Healthier, happier employees are more productive.",
      },
      {
        id: "3",
        question: "Improved Reputation",
        answer: "Demonstrate your commitment to employee wellbeing.",
      }, 
    ],
  };
  
  export default EmployeeWellnessData;
  